method123.com 2008-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Method123 : Project Management templates, free risk tools

Method123 is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of individuals we deal with. 

  **How we use your personal information**

  We only use the personal information obtained from you to respond to, and process your request for our goods and services. We do not sell personal information to any other organisations or companies, including those related to us. 

  We will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others without first obtaining your consent, unless required to do so by law. 

  We may monitor this website (including using 'cookies') in order to identify user trends, which will assist us in improving the site. If that occurs, the information will only be used in aggregate form and your individual details will not be identified or disclosed to any person. 

  **Accuracy of personal information**

  We take all reasonable steps to ensure that all personal information we hold is as accurate as is possible. You have the right to contact us at any time and ask for its correction if you feel the personal information we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete. In normal circumstances we would correct that information. If we do not, you are entitled to request that we attach to that information a statement provided by you of the correction requested but not made. 

  **Security of personal information**

  We use security procedures and technology to protect the personal information we hold. We have procedures in place to prevent loss, unauthorised access, use, modification, disclosure or other misuse of your personal information. If other organisations support our information systems, we require them to appropriately safeguard the privacy of personal information we may provide to them. 

  If you have registered login access to secure parts of this website, your account information is password protected. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. To further protect your personal information, your log-in time will automatically expire after a specified period of inactivity. 

  We will delete personal information that is no longer required by us. 

  **Information gathered on this website**

  When you browse, read or download information from our website our system may log these movements. These website logs (save where they relate to the unique license number created when you purchase a licence to use our templates) are not personally identifiable and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals who browse our website. 

  **Links**

  We cannot provide any assurances or take any responsibility for the privacy practices of websites to which we provide links. 

  **Accessing your personal information**

  You have the right to request access to your information. We will usually give you full access to your personal information but, in some cases there may be legal or administrative reasons that prevent your access. If we deny access then we will inform you of the reasons why. 

  Please contact us if you would like to know more about how you can access or update your personal information.
